Exercise 7-2. Reduce sounds. Read aloud from the right-hand column. The intonation
is marked for you. To. Today. Tonight. Tomorrow. To work. To school. To the
store. We have to go now. He went to work. They hope to find it. can't wait to find
out. We don't know what to do. Don't jump to conclusions. To be or not to be. He
didn't get to go. He told me to help. She told you to get it. I go to work at a
quarter to two. The only way to get it is you've got to pay to get it. We plan to do
it. Let's go to lunch. The score was four to six. It's the only way to do it, so to
speak. I don't know how to say it. Go to page eight. Show me how to get it. You
need to know when to do it. Who's to blame? At. We're at home. I'll see you
Dinner's at five. Leave him at the door. The meeting's at one. He's at the post
office. They're at the bank. I'm at school. I'll see you at eleven. He's at a
meeting. She laughed at his idea. One at a time. We got it at an auction. The show
started at eight. The dog jumped out at us. I was at a friend's house. It. Can you
do it? Give it to me. Buy it tomorrow. It can wait. Read it twice. Forget about it.
Give it a try. Let it alone. Take it away. I got it in London. What is it about?
Let's try it again. Look, there it is. Four. This is for you. It's for my friend.
A table for four, please. We planned it for later. For example, for instance, what
is this for? What'd you do it for? Who'd you get it for? From. It's from the IRS.
I'm from Arkansas. There's a letter from Bob. This letter's from Alaska. Who's it
from? Where are you from? In. It's in the bag. It's in it. I'll be back in a minute.
This movie? Who's in it? Come in. He's in America. N. He's an American. I got an A
in English. He got an F in Algebra. He had an accident. We want an orange. He didn't
have an excuse. I'll be there in an instant. It's an easy mistake to make. And
ham and eggs, bread and butter, coffee with cream and sugar, no, lemon and sugar,
and some more cookies. They kept going back and forth. We watched it again and
again. He did it over and over. We learned by trial and error. Or soup or salad, now
or later, more or less, left or right, for here to go. Are you going up or down? R.
What are you doing? Where are you going? What are you planning on doing? How are
you? Those are no good. How are you doing? The kids are still asleep. Your. How's
your family? Where are your keys? You're American, aren't you? Tell me when you're
ready. Is this your car? You're late again, Bob. Which one is yours? One. Which
one is better? One of them is broken. Use the other one. I like the red one Edwin
That's the last one The next one will be better Here's one for you Let him go one
by one The it's the best What's the matter? What's the problem? I have to go
to the bathroom Who's the boss around here? Give it to the dog Put it in the
drawer. Ah. It's a present. You need a break. Give him a chance. Let's get a new
pair of shoes. Can I have a Coke, please? Is that a computer? Where's a public
telephone? Of. It's the top of the line. It's a state of the art printer. As a
matter of fact, get out of here. practice all of the time. Today's the first of May.
What's the name of that movie? That's the best of all. Some of them. All of them.
Most of them. None of them. Any of them. The rest of them. Can. Can you speak
English? I can only do it Wednesday. A can opener can open cans. Can I help you? Can
you do it? We can try it later. I hope you can sell it. No one can fix it. Let me
know if you can find it. Had. Jack had had enough. Bill had forgotten again. What did
he do to deserve it? We'd already seen it. He'd never been there. Had you ever had
one? Where'd he hidden it? Bob said he'd looked into it. Would. He would have
helped if. Would he like one? Do you think he'd do it? Why would I tell her? We'd see
it again if. He'd never be there on time. Would you ever have one? Was. help. Mark
was American. Where was it? How was it? That was great. Who was with you? She was
very clear. When was the war of 1812? What? What time is it? What's up? What's
on your agenda? What do you mean? What'd you mean? What'd you do about it? What
took so long? What do you think of this? What'd you do then? I don't know what he
wants. Some. Some are better than others. There are some leftovers. Let's buy some
ice cream. Could we get some other ones? Take some of mine. Would you like Do you
like s'more? Do you have some ice? Do you have some ice?